// Creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [{
        numb: 1,
        question: 'Which of the following is not JavaScript Data Types?',
        answer: 'Float',
        options: [
            'Undefined',
            'Number',
            'Boolean',
            'Float'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: 'Which company developed JavaScript?',
        answer: 'Netscape',
        options: [
            'Netscape',
            'Bell Labs',
            'Sun Microsystems',
            'IBM'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: 'What are the types of Pop up boxes available in JavaScript?',
        answer: 'Alert',
        options: [
            'Alert',
            'Prompt',
            'Confirm',
            'All of the above',
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: 'Which of the following is not Javascript frameworks or libraries?',
        answer: 'Cassandra',
        options: [
            'Polymer',
            'Meteor',
            'Cassandra',
            'jQuery'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: 'Why so JavaScript and Java have similar name?',
        answer: "JavaScript's syntax is loosely based on Java's",
        options: ['JavaScript is a stripped-down version of Java',
            "JavaScript's syntax is loosely based on Java's",
            'They both originated on the island of Java ',
            'None of the above'
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 6,
        question: 'What is the original name of JavaScript?',
        answer: 'Mocha',
        options: [
            'LiveScript',
            'EScript',
            'Mocha',
            'JavaScript'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: 'Which of the following is correct about features of JavaScript?',
        answer: 'JavaScript is a object-based scripting language.',
        options: [
            'It can not Handling dates and time.',
            'JavaScript is a object - based scripting language.',
            'JavaScript is not interpreter based scripting language.',
            'All of the above'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 8,
        question: 'Choose the correct JavaScript syntax to change the content of the following HTML code.',
        answer: 'document.getElementById (“letsfindcourse").innerHTML = "I am a letsfindcourse";',
        options: [
            'document.getElement (“letsfindcourse").innerHTML = "I am a letsfindcourse";',
            'document.getElementById(“letsfindcourse ").innerHTML = "I am a letsfindcourse ";',
            'document.getId(“letsfindcourse ") = "I am a letsfindcourse ";',
            'document.getElementById(“letsfindcourse ").innerHTML = I am a letsfindcourse;'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: 'Which of the following is the correct syntax to display "Letsfindcourse" in an alert box using JavaScript ?',
        answer: 'alert("Letsfindcourse");',
        options: [
            'alert-box("Letsfindcourse");',
            'confirm("Letsfindcourse");',
            'msgbox("Letsfindcourse");',
            'alert("Letsfindcourse");'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: 'Which of them is not the looping structures in JavaScript?',
        answer: 'confirm',
        options: [
            'for',
            'while',
            'confirm',
            'all of the above'
        ]
    },
]